miamiandbeaches.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy and UGC Terms

### When you use our services, you're trusting us with your information. We understand how important your privacy is and work hard to protect your information.

**This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information we collect, why we collect it, and how you can update, manage, export, and delete your information.**

**I. Policy Statement Overview**  
This document describes the Greater Miami Convention & Visitors Bureau (hereafter referred to as GMCVB) policy regarding personal information, ongoing communication, site security and overall site usage of MiamiandBeaches.com and DiscoverMiamiBeach.com as well as other digital services and offerings and websites we provide. These provisions apply solely to online activities and are not necessarily applicable to practices GMCVB may engage in outside of our digital services and offerings. Use of this website and digital services signifies your acceptance of the terms and conditions of use set forth in this document. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not access or otherwise use this website.

**II. Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
We want you to understand the types of information we collect as you use our services.

We use various technologies to collect and store information, including cookies, pixel tags, local storage, such as browser web storage or application data caches, databases, and server logs.

The GMCVB is the data controller for all information collected through online digital channels and can be contacted here:  
Greater Miami Convention & Visitors Bureau  
Attn: Office of Digital Marketing and Advertising  
701 Brickell Avenue  
Suite 2700  
Miami, FL 33131 USA

**II.1. What Information We Collect**  
The information collected on our digital platforms is used to determine important statistical data for the GMCVB, its partners and members to determine the effectiveness of the content, programs and advertisements offered through our website. We also collect information to provide better services to all our users — from things like which language you speak, to more complex things like which ads you'll find most useful, the interests that matter most to you online, or which videos you might like to watch. The information the GMCVB collects, and how that information is used, depends on how you use our services and how you manage your privacy controls.

The GMCVB, its partners and affiliates collect personal contact and demographic information that the consumer willingly provides such as name, address, zip code and email address with the intention of using this information for purposes of statistical reporting and targeted promotional campaigns. Contact information may be used to send administrative and promotional materials from the GMCVB and/or its partners and affiliates. We do not collect or store sensitive data such as Race or ethnic origin, Political opinions, Religious or philosophical beliefs, Trade union memberships, Genetic or biometric data, Health or mortality, Sex life or sexual orientation.

We also collect behavioral data based on user's preferences to enhance the user digital experiences and interactions, which includes products that are integrated into third-party apps and sites, like ads and embedded maps. We also receive information from advertisers to provide advertising and research services on their behalf. You always have the option of discontinuing the remittance of these by contacting us (please see Opt-In / Opt-Out, below).

When signed in to a GMCVB website or app, we collect data such as unique identifiers, browser type and settings, device type and settings, operating system, mobile network information including carrier name, and application version number. We also collect information about the interaction of your apps, browsers, and devices with our services, including IP address, crash reports, system activity, and the date, time, and referrer URL of your request.

We collect this information when a service on your device contacts our servers — for example, when you install an app from the Play Store or when a service checks for automatic updates. If you're using a mobile device, your device may periodically contact our servers to provide information about your device and connection to our services. This information includes things like your device type, carrier name, crash reports, and which apps you've installed.

We also collect information that we store with your account, which we treat as personal information and can include information about your activity in our services, which we use to do things like recommend content you might like. We may collect information about your location when you use our services, which helps us offer features like driving directions for your weekend getaway or restaurants you have previously shown an interest in that are near you.

When you're not signed in to a GMCVB Account, we store the information we collect with unique identifiers tied to the browser, application, or device you're using. This helps us do things like maintain your language preferences across browsing sessions. We use the information we collect to customize our services for you, including providing recommendations, personalized content, and customized search results.

We use data for analytics and measurement to understand how our services are used. For example, we analyze data about your visits to our sites to do things like optimize product design. And we also use data about the ads you interact with to help advertisers understand the performance of their ad campaigns. We use a variety of tools to do this, including analytics.

We use different technologies to process your information for these purposes. We use automated systems that analyze your content to provide you with things like customized search results, personalized ads, or other features tailored to how you use our services. And we analyze your content to help us detect abuse such as spam, malware, and illegal content. We also use algorithms to recognize patterns in data.

**III. Security of Personal Information**  
We exercise reasonable care to protect your non-public personal information. This includes storing the personal information on our servers behind a secured firewall and ensuring all transmissions to other vendors use secure encryption technology.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. So while we strive to protect your non-public personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. This is especially true for information you transmit to us via email. We have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. Once we receive your transmission, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.

Internally, we will limit access to non-public personal information to those associates who need the information to provide products and services to you or maintain or service those products or services. These associates are limited in number, and are committed to our privacy and security policies. We will review our security arrangements from time to time, as we deem appropriate.

**IV. Sharing of Non-Public Personal Information**  
We reserve the right to, without notice to you, share non-public personal information with companies that work for us for the sole purpose of providing you with valuable services you've requested or already have. These companies may assist us in fulfilling your requests or processing your transactions.

We will only share information with companies that work for us to provide marketing and other services and with non-affiliated persons and entities with whom we have entered into a joint marketing agreement, where we together market either our products or those of our marketing partner if you expressly authorize us to share this information. These companies are contractually forbidden from disclosing or using our customer information other than to carry out the purposes for which the information was disclosed. These companies are in no way authorized to sell, rent or trade your personal information. While there are such contractual obligations in place, we cannot and do not guarantee that a third party could breach its obligation and use your non-public personal information in a way contrary to our policy.

We may disclose information, including non-public personal information, in special cases when we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with the legal process such as, but not limited to situations when we are required to do so by federal, state or local laws and regulations or when we receive a subpoena or are ordered by a court to do so; (b) protect and defend our rights; or (c) act to protect the interests of our users or others. Additionally, we may, without notice to you, provide aggregate statistics about visitors to MiamiandBeaches.com, such as volume, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal information.

**V. Email Communication from GMCVB**  
You will only receive email from the GMCVB if you have registered on one of our digital platforms, signed up to receive promotional or other information, have communicated with us via email and/or requested a response via email. We use information we collect, like your email address, to interact with you directly. These emails may let you know about upcoming changes or improvements to our services as well as optional opt-in promotional information such as special offers or visitor information. If you are currently on our list and do not wish to receive further information from us, see Opt-In / Opt-Out, below.

**VI. Opt-In / Opt-Out**  
When you're signed in, you can always review and update privacy information and communication permissions by visiting your user profile link on the site. You may choose to remove yourself from our mailing list by following the "Unsubscribe" instructions stated on our emails.

**VII. Contests/Sweepstakes Information**  
Participation in featured/sponsored contests and sweepstakes also requires the disclosure of contact and demographic information. This information is required to contact you as necessary. It may also be used to send you promotional information. However, you may opt-out of or opt-in to our mailings at any time. (See Opt-In / Opt-Out, above.)

**VIII. Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Similar Technologies**  
We use cookies and similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels, ad tags and device identifiers) to recognize you and/or your device(s) on, off and across different Services and devices.

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you provide to us on the Site, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically collect certain Site usage information whenever you visit or interact with the Site. This information may include browser type, operating system, the web page served, the time, and the preceding web page viewed, among other information. We may use this Site usage information for a variety of purposes, including to enhance or otherwise improve the Site. In addition, your IP address or some other unique identifier for the particular device you use to access the Site, as applicable (each, a "Device Identifier") may be collected. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer, your mobile phone, or other device used to access the Internet (each, a "Device"), and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier. We may associate your Device Identifier with your Personal Information. We may use cookies, web beacons, embedded scripts and other technologies to collect Site usage information.

_Cookies._ A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to access the Site. Cookies may be used for many purposes including, without limitation, tracking user preferences and web pages visited while using the Site. You may disable cookies using your Device's preferences, but some features of the Site may not function properly if you disable cookies.

_Web Beacons._ Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons (also known as "1×1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs") may be included in the Site's web pages and e-mail messages. Web beacons may be invisible to you, but any image or other web programming code inserted into a web page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Site, to monitor how users navigate the Site, to count how many e-mails sent were actually opened or to count how many particular videos or links were actually viewed.

_Embedded Scripts._ An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as which links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our Web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.

We may combine automatically collected Site usage information with your Personal Information. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information.

_Tracking and Ad Tags._ Google Analytics Advertising features have been enabled on our website: Interest-based Advertising, including Remarketing; DoubleClick Platform integration; Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features enable Google Analytics to collect data about our website traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation.

GMCVB and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. These cookies are also used by the GMCVB and third-party vendors to inform, optimize, and serve ads across the Internet based on someone's past visits to our website.

Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web can be [found here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You may also [download the DoubleClick advertising cookie opt-out plugin](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin).

Google Analytics Advertising features have been enabled on our website: Interest-based Advertising, including Remarketing; DoubleClick Platform integration; Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features enable Google Analytics to collect data about our website traffic via Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation.

GMCVB and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. These cookies are also used by the GMCVB and third-party vendors to inform, optimize, and serve ads across the Internet based on someone's past visits to our website.

We will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google advertising product or feature unless we have notice of and the user's prior affirmative (ie: opt-in) consent to that merger.

Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web can be [found here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You may also download the DoubleClick advertising cookie opt-out plugin [here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/7395996).

**IX. User Generated Content Posted by You**  
We may provide you with the ability to rate or review products or services, or otherwise post content on our website our through our social media channels as well as integrate with third-party review platforms such as Google or Trip Advisor to which you may have previously provided content. Any comments or reviews that you provide are accessible to all users of the relevant platform and may be visible to others or collected by third-parties, so you should use discretion when posting information and you should not post personal information. If you do post personal information, you do so at your own risk.

See below for complete User Generated Content Terms and Conditions

**X. Third Party Links**  
Our digital platforms contains links to other sites, including those of our business partners. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites and those other sites have not agreed to our privacy policy. Visit those sites for information regarding their privacy policy prior to providing personal information.

The links we provide are there for your reference and convenience. We do not control any of these websites, nor are we responsible for their content. The GMCVB does not imply any endorsement of the material on such websites or any association with their operators by including these links. If you decide to access any of these websites you do so entirely at your own risk and you should be aware that upon using these links you will leave our digital platforms.

**XI. Indemnification**  
You hereby agree to indemnify, defend and hold the GMCVB, and all its officers, directors, owners, agents, employees, information providers, affiliates, licensors and licensees (collectively, the "Indemnified Parties") harmless from and against any and all liability and costs incurred by the Indemnified Parties in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by you of the Agreement or the foregoing representations, warranties and covenants, including, without limitation, attorneys fees and costs.

**XII. Modification of Terms and Conditions**  
GMCVB reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove any portion of this Agreement, in whole or in part, at any time. Notification of changes in the Agreement will be posted on the website. GMCVB may change, suspend or discontinue any aspect of the website at any time, including the availability of any website feature, database, or content. GMCVB may also impose limits on certain features and services or restrict your access to parts or all of the website without notice or liability. By using this website you agree to be bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit the page to determine the then current terms of use to which you are bound.

If you have any questions, please contact us at:  
Greater Miami Convention & Visitors Bureau  
Attn: Office of Digital Marketing and Advertising  
701 Brickell Avenue  
Suite 2700  
Miami, FL 33131 USA

### Complete Terms and Conditions for User-Generated Content

**Terms and Conditions**  
Content Creators retain all ownership of the content and only grant limited rights to Licensee and subsidiaries or assigns as described in the content license terms outlined below and otherwise communicated (e.g. in a particular request). For good and valuable consideration, Greater Miami Convention and Visitors Bureau (GMCVB) (the “Licensee”) and Content Creator (the “Creator”) agree as follows:

**Term.**  
The term of this Agreement (the "Term") shall commence upon the date of acceptance by Creator and shall continue until terminated by Licensee. Written request for termination may be submitted to socialmedia@gmcvb.com .

**Proprietary Rights.**  
Creator upon acceptance of this agreement hereby grants Licensee a worldwide, non-exclusive, irrevocable, royalty-free, transferable license to reproduce, distribute, display and to create derivative works from the materials contained in the requested work (the “Post”).

**Promotional Use.**  
Creator grants to Licensee the right to use Creator's user name, profile image, pseudonym and/or image in connection with authorized uses of the Post.

**Credit, Attribution and Linking.**  
Licensee may give Creator credit in connection with the use of the Post by identifying Creator in conjunction with the content of the Post as displayed. Licensee may also provide a link to the Post, to the extent available, on the source network (e.g. Instagram, Facebook, Twitter).

**Warranties and Representations.**  
Creator warrants and represents that the Posts are Creator's original works, and do not now and will not violate any existing intellectual property rights, including, without limitation, copyright or trade secret or any contractual rights, and that they contain no matter which, if published, will be fraudulent, harassing, libelous, obscene, or a violation of any rights of publicly or privacy, or any law or regulation. Author will fully cooperate with Licensee in responding to and defending against any third party claim related to the Post.

**Indemnity.**  
Each Party hereto shall indemnify, defend, and hold harmless the other Party, its editors, officers, employees and agents with respect to any claim, demand, cause of action, debt or liability, including reasonable \ attorneys' fees, to the extent that it is based upon a claim that, if true, would constitute a breach of any of the indemnifying Party's representations, warranties, or agreements hereunder.

**Arbitration.**  
YOU AGREE THAT DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND LICENSEE WILL BE RESOLVED BY BINDING, INDIVIDUAL ARBITRATION AND YOU WAIVE YOUR RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT OR CLASSWIDE ARBITRATION.

**Entire Agreement.**  
These Terms of and Conditions, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and Licensee regarding the Post content and supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals (whether oral, written or electronic) between you and Licensee.
